var myQuestions = [
    {
        question : "1. Not a marvel superhero",
        answers: ["Thor", "Daredevil", "Black Widow", "The flash"],
        correct: "The flash",
        name : 0
    },
    {
        question : "2. Do the math, 1000 + 10 + 1000 + 20 + 1000 + 30 + 1000 + 40",
        answers: ["4010", "4100", "4200", "5000"],
        correct: "4100",
        name : 1
    },
    {
        question : "3. What is the color of the stars in the flag of the United States of America?",
        answers: ["Red", "Blue", "White", "Black"],
        correct: "White",
        name : 2
    },
    {
        question : "4. What's the total number of dots on a pair of dice?",
        answers: ["41", "42", "43", "44"],
        correct: "42",
        name : 3
    },
    {
        question : "5.Traditionally, how many Wonders of the World are there?",
        answers: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        correct: "7",
        name : 4
    },
    {
        question : "6. What is the chemical symbol for Hydrogen?",
        answers: ["H", "He", "Hy", "Hg"],
        correct: "H",
        name : 5
    },
    {
        question : "7. How many sides does an octagon have?",
        answers: ["Six", "Seven", "Eight", "nine"],
        correct: "Eight",
        name : 6
    },
    {
        question : "8.Which part of the body would a chiropodist treat?",
        answers: ["Hands", "Head", "Feet", "Back"],
        correct: "Feet",
        name : 7
    },
    {
        question : "9. What is the name of the city where the cartoon family The Simpsons live?",
        answers: ["Hollywood", "Scottsdale", "Summerfield", "Springfield"],
        correct: "Springfield",
        name : 8
    },
    {
        question : "10. Which U.S. president appears on the front of the $2 bill?",
        answers: ["Thomas Jefferson", "Abraham Lincoln", "George Washington", "Benjamin Franklin"],
        correct: "Thomas Jefferson",
        name : 9
    }
]
